The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
After barging into the Black Bull's hideout unannounced,
Meraleona marched out with Asta and company in tow.
Their destination, the Yoltim Volcano,
a strong magic region where Asta and Noelle
had previously trained with the Crimson Lion Kings.
There, Meraleona and Voigoleon had arranged another training session
in preparation for their battle with the Devil.
Let's race to the top so we can hit that sweet hot spring!
Hold it!
There'll be no climbing this time.
Instead, I'm going to have you venture below.
To the underground cave!
As the young wizards approached the hot springs that marked the end of their path,
they encountered a new mana blazing with an intensity they had never seen before.
But then...
Eat this!
Flame magic!
Viral flame!
A powerful spell from Leopold was enough to ward off the monstrous spider.
And soon after, another of the cave's secrets was revealed.
Where does that door lead to?
Ah!
Dungeons!
This ought to be interesting.
Villainemöl
In the next episode,
110 sensualzy
Post-Rawful
Part소
If you areечение,
風吹く世界の果てで僕らは今日も目を閉じる夢を見る飽きもせず
今は小さく儚い希望もいつか時代を変えてゆく光になると信じて背負うべきものなど何一つないさ全て抱きしめてゆく
例えばそれが痛みだとしても叶うなら君と共に
この声がこの喉が振り切れるほど今叫ぶよ
未来は自分で切り開くんだってとめとなく溢れ出る情熱のままさ歩き出そう
風吹く世界の夢を見る
2018発表
チーム明真理光
心の意味込む
サンフレオネと迷众
Captain Merleona, what's happening here?
You're late!
You weren't called out here for a leisurely stroll with your Black Bull buddies, you weaklings!
You call yourselves Crimson Lion Kings!
We beg your forgiveness.
We would have gotten here faster if it had been just the Vice-Captain and me.
We are unworthy of our station.
And you?
Nobody gave you permission to eat!
Oh, come on, Charmy, read the room, would you? This really isn't the time for a snack!
We've already reported our discovery to the Royal Capital. You are to wait here for instructions.
Yes, sir!
What?
Hold on, are you saying that giant spider came after you guys, too?
Yeah, and just like that, that thing bugged off into some mystery dungeon.
Right? I'm so ready!
Ready for what?
I was a fool to let that spider escape.
This can't be how it ends.
Sister!
We wish to explore that dungeon as well!
Don't get cocky!
You're the incompetent weakling who let that bug get away to begin with, fool!
You've got some nerve asking anything of me after that!
But next time, I know I can defeat it!
There is no next time in battle!
Now get your head on straight by fighting your way through that dungeon!
Yes, ma'am.
Man, she's still as hot blooded as ever!
Wasn't that exactly what he was asking for?
All eyes up here!
Alright then, Captain Foygolion filled me in.
Deep in that dungeon you discovered, we believe there's a powerful magic item.
According to a book that Master Julius found in the library, it was sealed away somewhere inside the Yoltam Volcano centuries ago,
out of fear that its power might someday be used for evil.
Unfortunately, the records contain nothing specific about the item itself.
That's right! It's a total mystery!
I don't need help explaining.
Now please be quiet!
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm just so excited to learn about this long-lost mystery artifact.
Actually, can I go there too?
Absolutely not!
Why? I'll wear a disguise!
It's entirely beside the point!
Who do you think he's talking to? I'm not sure.
Yeah, I know that voice.
The Wizard King.
In any case, this magic item will be key in restoring our kingdom,
along with any other treasure you might find inside the dungeon.
I ask that you all conduct your search thoroughly.
Understood.
Now then!
Listen here, fools!
You're all staking your pride as magic knights on this!
Do it for your kingdom!
Yes, ma'am!
Please, sister.
As the current captain, I should be the one to conclude this briefing.
Fine.
Hurry up and get on with it.
Asta, Noelle, Leo, Randall, Luck, and Magna.
You are to take the lead and locate the magic item.
The rest of you will rendezvous with these six as soon as your mana has recovered.
I'm just gonna head down there real quick.
You will do no such thing.
I'm ready.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Ouch!
Damn, I thought it was hot before, but that was nothing compared to this.
I don't sense that spider's mana at all.
Uh-oh.
Skillfully done, rifle.
You've disarmed the first trap already.
It's not like I did that on purpose.
We can't afford to get bogged down here for too long.
He used just enough power to reveal them without triggering them.
That was high-level magic.
And he made it look easy.
So that's the vice-captain of the Crimson Lion Kings.
Now that they're all lit up like this, we can spot these traps with our eyes shut.
Later, you guys!
Lightning creation magic!
Holy lightning boost!
I wasn't ready!
Flame reinforcement magic!
Risky stolen base!
Hey!
Don't set him off in front of me!
Well, Asta, looks like the middle path's been claimed,
so let's split up here.
Whichever team finds the magic item first, wins the race!
All right, you're on!
I'm amazed Leo can move so easily in mana this dense.
We need to be quick, vice-captain Randall!
Got it.
I have to say, Leo,
it's obvious that you've been training far harder than anyone else in the squad.
And yet, I'm still not strong enough to catch up with my rival,
let alone surpass him!
In his recent battle,
Asta went toe-to-toe with the Devil,
and won.
What's more,
I heard that the other Black Bulls also fought valiantly.
This training can hardly compare.
So that's it.
Now I see why the captains invited the Black Bulls to take part in this exercise with us.
Don't sell yourself short, Leo.
I think that last battle brought you to the verge of a breakthrough.
It hit you when you had to face off with me after that elf took over my body.
I'm sure I could sense violent intent in that surge of mana just now.
Let's check it out.
Come on!
It's only gonna get worse if we can't smash our way through this!
Charging through a dungeon full of traps might be fine for a meathead like you,
but that's not how I do things, okay?
Then just let me carry you!
Huh?
You can hop on my back and keep casting spells while I get us out of here!
You want me to hop on your back?
I refuse!
I'm royalty, and that's beneath my dignity!
Let's go!
Asta?
Wait a sec, why are we turning around?
We're-we're pulling back for now!
A-ha!
Is this...
Look up!
Those must be the golems that were guarding this place.
Stay sharp.
The spider may have sent out that blast of violent mana before because it wanted us to find it.
It might be trying to draw us into a trap.
You won't escape from me this time, bug!
I'll use my raging inferno and burn them all to ash!
We've finished neutralizing all the trap spells near the entrance.
Good.
Take a moment to recover your mana, and then widen the search.
Yes, ma'am.
Go on, eat up everybody!
Did you find anything?
No, thanks to Asta, we got to waste our time running away from a huge wave of lava instead.
Yep, happy to help.
We actually found a bunch of weird-ass treasure chests, but I didn't grab any because...
They have legs!
Yeah!
What is that?
Why did you bring that back with you? Don't even think about opening it!
Oh, God.
Close that thing already!
You think we could eat that?
I would rather not find out.
What was that?
The only ones who were still unaccounted for from the first group are Randall and Leo.
I suppose this means those two are our lucky winners, then.
Let's do this!
Yes, sir!
Perish in flames!
There are just too many of them to handle.
But we are the proud Crimson Lion Kings, and we will never run away from the battlefield!
Hold on!
Leo!
No!
Randall!
Hurry up and get out of here, Leo!
You have to survive, no matter what!
Leo, there's no doubt you're going to become the leader of this squad someday.
So let us buy you a little time.
Please, get out of this place and live.
Take the wounded with you.
It's happening again.
What have I been training so hard for all this time?
What was that?
Don't sell yourself short, Leo.
I think that last battle brought you to the verge of a breakthrough.
That's right.
When I fought Randall, I was caught inside his powerful mana field for the entire battle.
None of my attacks could reach him.
But I was still able to read his mana and maintain complete control over my flames.
Leo!
Now it's time to get a little crazy in here.
Hope you guys put up a good fight before I kill you.
That spider has committed a grave sin.
It devoured tons of undiscovered ingredients before I could.
I'm going to make you pay for hurting my friends.
Now begin the counterattack.
Water creation magic.
Sea dragons roar!
This spell seems more powerful than before.
Is that because of my training?
Two on this!
Flame magic!
Gargantuan exploding fireball!
Lightning magic!
Thunderbolt destruction!
Poison curse magic.
Dwelling of the poison cloud.
Cotton creation magic!
Strike of the sleeping sheep!
Go secure Vice Captain Randall.
Roger that!
There's a ton of them.
We gotta stop the spider.
It's the one controlling those things with its webs.
Let's finish this.
No.
It's my turn.
Hmm?
I had a breakthrough.
And it's time to make use of it.
By pushing his senses to their limits and calmly reading the flow of mana surrounding him,
Leopold is able to momentarily manipulate it, combining it with his own mana for an explosive increase in power.
That was totally incredible!
This must be the spider's original form.
It seems this magic item causes its user's life force to grow out of control.
And in the process, the power overload turns them into a monster.
Excellent work in finding the treasure room.
The trial you've endured here today will surely leave all of you better prepared for your coming battle with the devil.
Yes, sir!
It took a while, but I think I'm starting to get the hang of this mana skin thing.
And I can tell my spells are getting more powerful.
Speaking of, did everyone else see that crazy strong spell Leo whipped out right at the end?
It happened so fast, I barely know what I did.
What was that spell?
And how do I control it?
Ha ha ha!
Yes, rival, be amazed!
Soon I shall master that spell and become stronger than you!
Then I'll just have to get stronger than you!
Then I'll be forced to become stronger still!
I'll get even stronger then!
Then I'll simply have to keep on getting stronger!
I'll keep getting even stronger and stronger and stronger and stronger!
Let's stop your shouting!
Yes, ma'am!
This mission isn't over yet.
Not until the magic item is secured.
Right, here you go.
What is this?
What do you mean?
It's the magic item.
It's a damn lump of coal, you absolute fools!
Bringing back that magic item was our primary objective on this mission.
How could you idiots burn it to ash like this?
You're right.
We beg for your forgiveness.
You're going back in and searching that dungeon from end to end,
and you will not return empty-handed!
Yes, ma'am!
Wait, really?
Come on, you can't be serious!
She's serious.
Dead serious?
She's totally serious.
Everybody else, get to the hot springs!
Yes, ma'am!
Drink up!
Well, I'm still not sure what all those ingredients are that I found in the dungeon,
so I just squeezed anything that looked like it might have juice in it
and mixed it all up into this one super-special thirst-quenching dungeon drink!
I have to admit, this bath is nice.
It looks like you've been getting a bit closer to your mother.
That form you used in your last battle, you were the living image of the steel warrior princess, Lady Asier.
You've still got a ways to go yet.
Right now, your magic's not nearly as strong.
Yeah, of course.
The truth is exactly what you suspected.
Asier Silva lost her life to a devil's curse.
And what's worse, anyone who speaks of Asier's fate will share it with her.
That's the cruel nature of the curse that befell your mother,
and within the real world, there's no way around it.
But that just means I have to get stronger.
Backing down is not an option.
Is that right?
So, um, while we're here, could you tell me a little bit more about my mother?
That could take a while.
That's fine.
Isn't this great?
Man, the Crimson Lion King's captain is crazy uptight.
He's like some freaky opposite version of Captain Yami.
Listen well.
These hot springs are more than a spot for an invigorating soak.
Yes, sir!
If the heat becomes too much to bear,
you must keep your composure and quench your body and soul in cold water,
and return to the bath and push to your limits once more.
Even as we relax, we must strive to overcome our weakness.
Yes, sir!
Furthermore, remember to cleanse your body before entering the bath,
and don't let your towels come in contact with the water.
Make sure to rinse off the shower and bathing areas of hot water after using...
My body and soul need a quench.
How long can the captain keep talking like this?
Have Asta and Leopold returned?
I hope they get a chance to strengthen their bonds
by washing each other's backs in the hot springs.
Yeah, we kept looking till morning,
and we still didn't find anything worth bringing with us.
Anyway, that's my day.
How were the springs?
Sweat the exhaustion straight out of me.
With all the collagen in those ingredients I found,
my skin feels smooth as silk!
She's not wrong.
If it weren't in a strong magic region,
I'd come here every day.
Your skin looks really smooth, too!
Hey, back off!
That was a lot of fun!
I hope we can train with them again soon!
Are you crazy?
That psycho kidnapped us and dragged us to a freaking volcano!
If I never see her again, it'll be too soon!
It'd be so funny if she was in there!
Come on, there's no way!
Ah!
Where are you?
She's actually here!
Oh, it's now!
Thank you.
There is only one there.
I'm not mistaken.
Here's the magic item!
And what's with all these weird treasure chests?
Envy me, rival, for I have discovered a treasure the likes of which our world has never seen!
Its legs go all the way down!
Oh man!
Those are pretty impressive, but take a look at this pair!
Now those are some big beefy man legs!
So buff!
They make me want to bust out a set of squats!
It seems we have no choice but to find out which of us can locate the greatest treasure chest in this dungeon!
You up for it?
Heck yeah!
You're wrong!
Where is it?
Having forgotten their mission entirely, Asta and Leopold continued goofing off through the night.
It is a day of great consequence for the House of Vermillion!
We straddle the line between life and death!
For today, we receive her!
Next time on Black Clover, page 134, those who have been gathered, let us welcome her with all we have!